<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Anish Saxena</title>
    <link>https://Anish-Saxena.github.io/authors/admin/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Anish Saxena</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>All rights reserved 2022</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2021 08:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	    <atom:link href="https://Anish-Saxena.github.io/authors/admin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>CUDA Programming</title>
      <link>https://Anish-Saxena.github.io/talk/cuda_programming/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Anish-Saxena.github.io/talk/cuda_programming/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Systems Reading Group- Basic Module</title>
      <link>https://Anish-Saxena.github.io/talk/sys_reading_group/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Anish-Saxena.github.io/talk/sys_reading_group/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A reading group aimed at making the audience comfortable with basic concepts of computer systems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;list-of-talks&#34;&gt;List of Talks&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Introductory session: &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1RDWVsxqU7TSILcLsWiZrVj5OlaEVJSoWhH-rPrjOtXg/edit?usp=drivesdk&#34;&gt;Drive Link&lt;/a&gt;. Aimed at introducing the field of systems to the audience, and the logistics of the reading group.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;useful-links&#34;&gt;Useful Links&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reading Material: &lt;a href=&#34;https://drive.google.com/open?id=1bS7p7_JSsNOuVQ2sE-o3hk09wrAb5wQp&#34;&gt;Drive Link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Video Lecture playlists:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Digital Logic Design: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL5Q2soXY2Zi_QedyPWtRmFUJ2F8DdYP7l&#34;&gt;YouTube Link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reference Books:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Computer Organization And Design, 5th Ed., Patterson &amp;amp; Hannessy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;topic-list&#34;&gt;Topic List&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The reader can follow this list to start their journey and learn the different concepts of computer systems in a coherent manner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Digital Design&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Digital Circuits: Combination and Sequential Circuits, introduction to hardware.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Drive link:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Digital Circuits I: Introduction to digital logic, logic gates and Karnaugh maps&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Digital Circuits II: Introduction to combinational logic, encoder/ decoders, multiplexors/ de-multiplexors&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Digital Circuits III: Introduction to Sequential logic, latches, flip-flops, counters&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Video lecture: Digital Logic Design
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lecture 1: Introduction to hardware design, motivation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Digital Circuit slides have been taken from Prof. Aloke Dutta&amp;rsquo;s ESC201 course&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Logic Design: Terminologies, Memory elements and introduction to ISA.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Drive link:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Logic Design I: basic terminologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Logic Design II: Memory elements, DRAM and SRAM&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Logic Design III: The Instruction Set Architecture&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Video lectures: Digital Logic Design
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lecture 5&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lecture 7- first 40 minutes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lecture 8- optional, first 30 minutes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reference Book: Computer Organization And Design, P&amp;amp;H
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Appendix B1 to B9&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Chapter 2- sections 2.1 to 2.3&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The ISA explained both in slides and in reference book is MIPS, which is helpful for understanding the concepts while not being too impractically far off from real-world ISAs like x86.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Logic Design slides have been taken from Prof. Mainak Chaudhuri&amp;rsquo;s CS220 course&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flush-based attack optimizations</title>
      <link>https://Anish-Saxena.github.io/talk/cache_optimizations/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Anish-Saxena.github.io/talk/cache_optimizations/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Presentation-cum-demonstration for Undergraduate Research Project for the Fall 2019 semester taken under &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cse.iitk.ac.in/users/biswap/&#34;&gt;Biswa&lt;/a&gt;&amp;lsquo;s guidance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The processor architecture community has, for decades, focused on providing the best possible performance in the smallest feasible footprint. Recently, though, there has been a shift in ideology. Now, the focus is on providing the optimum balance between performance and energy consumption, keeping the demands and priority of the user in mind. The key here is to tune the processor’s frequency and voltage to reduce energy consumption.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Algorithms to scale power consumption efficiently have been deployed both in hardware and in software. However, these algorithms have once again been designed with performance as the aim. The security aspects have not been paid much attention to, as is clear from the abundance of microarchitectural attacks that have sprung up over the past decade.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our focus is to analyze the effects of aggressive power scaling algorithms for the benefit and subsequently utilize them for the benefit of an attacker, to improve the accuracy and resolution of cache-based attacks. We critique the flush-based attacks to determine the scope for improvement. We then present a detailed analysis of one of the key components in flush-based attacks.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CLKscrew Attack</title>
      <link>https://Anish-Saxena.github.io/talk/clkscrew/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2019 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Anish-Saxena.github.io/talk/clkscrew/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Original research paper by Tang &lt;em&gt;et al.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The need for power- and energy-efficient computing has resulted in aggressive cooperative hardware-software energy management mechanisms on modern commodity devices. Most systems today, for example, allow software to control the frequency and voltage of the underlying hardware at a very fine granularity to extend battery life. Despite their benefits, these software-exposed energy management mechanisms pose grave security implications that have not been studied before.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this work, we present the CLKSCREW attack, a new class of fault attacks that exploit the security-obliviousness of energy management mechanisms to break security. A novel benefit for the attackers is that these fault attacks become more accessible since they can now be conducted without the need for physical access to the devices or fault injection equipment. We demonstrate CLKSCREW on commodity ARM/Android devices. We show that a malicious kernel driver (1) can extract secret cryptographic keys from Trustzone, and (2) can escalate its privileges by loading self-signed code into Trustzone. As the first work to show the security ramifications of energy management mechanisms, we urge the community to re-examine these security-oblivious designs.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DABANGG: Cache Attack Optimizations</title>
      <link>https://Anish-Saxena.github.io/project/car3s/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2019 11:29:15 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Anish-Saxena.github.io/project/car3s/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Leveraged hardware optimizations to improve timing-based cache attacks. Visit &lt;a href=&#34;https://car3s.github.io/dabangg/&#34;&gt;attack&amp;rsquo;s webpage&lt;/a&gt; for details.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Duration&lt;/strong&gt;: April 2019 to June 2020&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mentor&lt;/strong&gt;: Prof. Biswabandan Panda, CSE Dept. IIT Kanpur&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Memory Tracing for Mobile Architectures</title>
      <link>https://Anish-Saxena.github.io/project/qualcomm_compression/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2019 11:29:15 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Anish-Saxena.github.io/project/qualcomm_compression/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Analyzed compression and memory tracing techniques for mobile architectures.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Duration&lt;/strong&gt;: July 2020 to June 2021&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mentor&lt;/strong&gt;: Prof. Biswabandan Panda, CSE Dept. IIT Kanpur&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Funded by Qualcomm Research to improve the front-end and memory subsystem of Systems-on-Chip.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developed a framework to collect Memory &amp;amp; Data Traces (MDT) through emulation or natively for Android.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Modified QEMU, the emulator used by Android Studio, to collect MDT from Android 9.0 API with x86_64 ABI.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extended Valgrind, a memory profiling framework, collected MDT natively from ARMv8-based devices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extended ChampSim, a trace-driven simulator, utilized MDT and analyzed patterns to improve branch prediction, prefetching, and cache compression at LLC.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reconfigurable Space Antenna</title>
      <link>https://Anish-Saxena.github.io/project/space_antenna/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2019 06:31:20 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Anish-Saxena.github.io/project/space_antenna/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Introduction&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Designed SMA actuator and low-power motor based antenna with 1 rotational &amp;amp; 2 translational degrees of freedom, and planned its signal reception &amp;amp; transmission.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Duration&lt;/strong&gt;: January 2019 to February 2019&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mentor&lt;/strong&gt;: Dr. Sahil Kalra (PhD), Space Technology Cell, IIT Kanpur (presently, Assistant Professor, IIT Jammu)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developed mechanism for ISRO to allow movement of space antenna deployed in satellite with 2 translation degrees of freedom.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rendered 3D model using Autodesk Fusion, integrated low powered motor to allow rotational degree of freedom.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Utilized state memory alloy (SMA) actuator developed by Dr. Kalra to allow movement of axis of rotation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Planned to use ISRO’s NavIC chip to allow transmission and reception of signals to control the antenna.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Studied signal transmission protocols pertinent to NavIC in order to devise communication strategies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ZombieLoad Attack</title>
      <link>https://Anish-Saxena.github.io/talk/zombieload/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2019 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Anish-Saxena.github.io/talk/zombieload/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Original research paper by Schwarz &lt;em&gt;et al.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In early 2018, Meltdown first showed how to read arbitrary kernel memory from user space by exploiting side-effects from transient instructions. While this attack has been mitigated through stronger isolation boundaries between user and kernel space, Meltdown inspired an entirely new class of fault-driven transient execution attacks. Particularly, over the past year, Meltdown-type attacks have been extended to not only leak data from the L1 cache butalso from various other microarchitectural structures, including the FPU register file and store buffer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this paper, we present the ZombieLoad attack which uncovers a novel Meltdown-type effect in the processor’s previously unexplored fill-buffer logic. Our analysis shows that faulting load instructions (i.e., loads that have to be re-issued for either architectural or microarchitectural reasons) may transiently dereference unauthorized destinations previously brought into the fill buffer by the current or a sibling logical CPU. Hence, we report data leakage of recently loaded stale values across logical cores. We demonstrate ZombieLoad’s effectiveness in a multitude of practical attack scenarios across CPU privilege rings, OS processes, virtual machines, and SGX enclaves. We discuss both short and long-term mitigation approaches and arrive at the conclusion that disabling hyperthreading is the only possible workaround to prevent this extremely powerful attack on current processors.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Campus Sustainability Challenge</title>
      <link>https://Anish-Saxena.github.io/project/campus_sustainence/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2019 08:29:15 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Anish-Saxena.github.io/project/campus_sustainence/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Introduction&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Led a team of 6 individuals to identify problems in campus and implement innovative solutions to combat it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Duration&lt;/strong&gt;: October 2018 to December 2018&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Competition&lt;/strong&gt;: Inter IIT Tech Meet 2018, IIT Bombay&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Showcased the E-Waste Management Software developed in 2017 to display optimum treatment path, given some parameters&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Integrated Biogas capturing mechanisms with Drum Composting to save up-to 14% of PNG consumption in Hall messes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improved upon current composting practices by integrating Smart sensors for monitoring the state of compost&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Multi-node multi-GPU programming</title>
      <link>https://Anish-Saxena.github.io/project/gpu_bootcamp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2019 08:29:15 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Anish-Saxena.github.io/project/gpu_bootcamp/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Duration&lt;/strong&gt;: May 2021 to August 2021&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Affiliation&lt;/strong&gt;: NVIDIA India&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Created open-source tutorials and boot-camps for scalable multi-GPU programming for HPC applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developed codes with CUDA-aware MPI, NCCL, and NVSHMEM libraries and labs in Jupyter Notebooks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E-Waste Management Software</title>
      <link>https://Anish-Saxena.github.io/project/ewaste/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2019 08:10:20 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Anish-Saxena.github.io/project/ewaste/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Introduction&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;.NET framework based project for predictive analysis of best route to take in order to recycle E-waste given a set of initial parameters to consider&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Duration&lt;/strong&gt;: August 2017 to November 2017&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mentor&lt;/strong&gt;: Prof. Indranil Saha, CSE Dept. IIT Kanpur&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Uses GUI based forms for taking user surveys and performs DataBase Management using MS Excel&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Converts electronic gadgets input by the users into precise amounts of substances in E-waste&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implements self-designed algorithms to display best solutions for given set of data in a survey&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Accounts for economic factors, environmental factors and performs relative analysis&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Highly Scalable FFT on GPUs</title>
      <link>https://Anish-Saxena.github.io/project/fft_library/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2019 08:10:20 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Anish-Saxena.github.io/project/fft_library/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Introduction&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Extended Tarang, a parallel computational fluid dynamics simulator, to enable GPU-based FFTs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Duration&lt;/strong&gt;: February 2021 to August 2021&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mentor&lt;/strong&gt;: Prof. Mahendra Verma, Physics Dept. IIT Kanpur&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extended Tarang, a parallel computational fluid dynamics simulator, to enable GPU-based FFTs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developed MPI and CuFFT-XT-based variable precision 1D and 3D scalable forward and inverse FFTs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Achieved upto 1650× single-node speed-up over FFTW on DGX-A100 and linear strong and weak scaling.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Compared DGX-A100’s performance in PARAM Siddhi AI with EPCC Cirrus cluster with 6 V100 GPUs per node.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Computer Hardware &amp; Technologies</title>
      <link>https://Anish-Saxena.github.io/talk/hardware/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Anish-Saxena.github.io/talk/hardware/</guid>
      <description>&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Delivered a talk on introduction to computer hardware and related technologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sensitized audience to various components of a computer system.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Focused on rapid pace of innovation and performance increase in the world of hardware over the past few decades.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Endeavours</title>
      <link>https://Anish-Saxena.github.io/project/social/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jun 2018 08:40:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Anish-Saxena.github.io/project/social/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;descriptive-research-climatic-cycle-and-weather-regime&#34;&gt;Descriptive Research: Climatic Cycle and Weather Regime&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Introduction&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Led a group of 4 individuals to conduct a research and field based project on the topic of &amp;ldquo;Climatic Cycle and Weather Regime- Needs and Aspirations of Future Generations&amp;rdquo;.&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
Won the 2nd Prize at regional level in NCSC organized competition.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Duration&lt;/strong&gt;: August 2015 to September 2015&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Spread awareness on harms of E-Waste in schools and nearby localities through street plays, posters and public speeches&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collected data on E-Waste generation in the school through surveys&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Visited ISRO Ahmedabad to gather information on their state-of-the-art recycling techniques&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contacted various NGOs to help in collection and proper disposal of E-Waste&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;case-study-intersectionality-and-access&#34;&gt;Case Study: Intersectionality and Access&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Introduction&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Participated in a month long workshop on accessibility issues faced by different sections of society. Learnt about the implications of such issues and conducted a field project in Kheda district near Ahmedabad on the theme of Women Empowerment.&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
Received &amp;ldquo;Outstanding Social Action Project&amp;rdquo; certificate from ITSA International.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Duration&lt;/strong&gt;: August 2013 to September 2013&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Received a token grant from ITSA International&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Distributed study material to underprivileged students and reviewed their state of education&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conducted bi-weekly classes on basic education for 4 weeks for students&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
